# **Stephan Benchemoul**

Full Stack Web Developer

**Phone:** +972 (0) 544-522614 **Location:** Tel Aviv, Israel

Linkdin Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephan-benchemoul-38879320b/

Email: stephanbazbaz@gmail.com

Full Stack Web Developer. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, Node js, Strong background in project management and customer relations.

### **EXPERIENCE**

PWM 1.2020 till present

## Front end developer

Freelance Front end developer

**Recommendations** -

Orel Ohayon

tel +972504704047

**Inception** 3.2020 - 5.2020

QA

QA for Bookful book app

Self Employed 2008 - 2019

Sound Engineer / Music Production

Recording studio sound engineer, music producer

## **EDUCATION**

**John Bryce** 2019 - 2020

Diploma

Full Stack Web developer

Completed the course with honors

S.A.E Australia 2006-2008

Bachelor degree

Sound Engineering

#### **SKILLS**

- \*React
- \*Redux
- \*Material
- \*Node JS
- \*Angular
- \*Python
- \*SOL
- \*Mongo DB
- \*Vue

*Docker *Bootstrap	